(Bernadette(on phone):)Long story.
(Bernadette(on phone):)Why don't you go ahead and eat.
(Bernadette(on phone):)We're gonna be a while.
(Howard:)I'm telling you,
I'm not on drugs.
The government's out to get me!
(Alfred:)Now, one of the more exciting
things to be found recently
(Alfred:)is that Neanderthals
(Alfred:)and Homo sapiens frequently
mated with each other.
(Mary:)Well, that certainly explains
my marriage to Sheldon's father.
(laughs)
(Sheldon:)That's funny, because my father
was not a very clever man.
(Amy:)I'd be lost without you.
(utensil clinking on glass)
(Leonard:)Uh, I would like
to propose a toast
(Leonard:)to my wife and bride-to-be.
(Sheldon:)See, that's funny because...
(Amy:)Back to your phone.
(Scene:)Penny...
(Leonard:)I've always known I loved you,
(Leonard:)but this last year has shown me
(Leonard:)that I also love
being married to you.
(Leonard:)Thank you
for saying yes.